

MAHAMADI CONGO

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- +49 177 7420 577
- Priesestr, 12053 Berlin
- linkedin.com/in/mahamadi-congo
- mahamadicongo.com

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Full-Stack Developer Training DCI DIGITAL CAREER INSTITUTE

- Certificate of Achievement, 2019 - 2020
- 1-year full stack training with real-life projects.
- Covered Node.js, React, JavaScript, MongoDB, Git.

degree AOREMA(L.P.A)

 general baccalaureate graduate -2009

SKILLS

- Front End: JavaScript,
 TypeScript, HTML/CSS,
 ReactJS,Next.js, Bootstrap,
 Tailwind, Storybook, styled-components, GraphQL
- Back End: Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, GraphQL
- Tools & Systems: VSCode,
 Docker, Git, GitHub, GitLab,
 Jira, Figma

PROFILE

A passionate Software Developer with experience in both front-end and back-end development. Proficient in JavaScript, ReactJS, Node.js, and various frameworks. Strong problem-solving abilities and a track record of delivering quality software solutions in collaboration with development teams and stakeholders.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TA Europe

Software Developer

Oct 2021 - Jan 2024

- Design and develop software solutions for front-end applications in collaboration with the development team and stakeholders.
- Conduct feasibility tests for software prototypes and modify code to fix errors.

Zalando

Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

Intern Software Developer

• Developed and implemented software solutions for Zalando retail based on provided designs.

Staiy

Feb 2021 - Jun 2021

Intern Software Developer

- Developed and implemented software solutions based on Figma designs.
- Tested and refined software prior to rollout and released ad hoc product patches.

LANGUAGE

- France (First language)
- English (Advanced)
- German (Intermediate)

REFERENCE

Sebastian Frohwann

COO / Partner

Phone: +49 173 463 53 86

Patrick Da Silva

CTO (Chief Technology Officer)

Phone: +4917670228902